

EMMA SMITH HR MANAGER

mma.smith@gnail.com

- +39 999 999 999
- OLondon, England
- in inkedin.com/emma-smith

OBJECTIVE

Motivated, seasoned and proactive individual with more than 8 years of HR management. Background of repeated success implementing best practices and establishing effective HR Strategies. Driven to deliver the highest level of service in an efficient and professional manner.

SKILLS

- Communication
- HR Policies
- Management

LANGUAGES

- English: fluent
- French: native speaker
- Spanish: beginner level

HOBBIES

- Horse riding
- Going to the theatre
- Gardening

WORK EXPERIENCE

HR MANAGER - Disney Media & Entertainment 2018 - Present

- HR budget management for Recruitment and Development including phasing analysis and monthly reporting.
- Recruitment and Onboarding of talents for Sales, Marketing, Communications, Trade Marketing, Finance, Compatibility, Operations and HR from apprentices, interns, Young Graduates, VIEs and full time roles.
- Acted as a consultant to the CEO and Founder team in defining the organisational structure, job descriptions, roles and responsibilities for the eCommerce team.

HR MANAGER - Hollywood video 2014 – 2018

- Upskilled and train managers on best practice low level HR to allow them to take ownership and accountability of their times.
- Successfully set up a new entity and worked closely with legal and external bodies.
- Managed the recruiting process internally interviews / 2nd interviews / trials etc.
- Wrote and delivered weekly training sessions for sales team.

RECRUITMENT CONSULTANT - Nike 2012 – 2014

- Worked on the data migration project identifying and re-designing solutions tailored around our business model and way of operating.
- Provided candidates with a detailed feedback about their interview.

EDUCATION

HUMAN RESOURCES MASTER'S - University of 2010 – 2012

HUMAN RESOURCES DEGREE – Keele University **2007** - **2010**

REFERENCES

James KNIGHT

Director

DISNEY Media & Entertainment

135 Heygate St, London, England

999 9999 9999

james.knight@gnail.com

Robert COOPER

Head of HR Resources

HOLLYWOOD VIDEO

Garden Row, London, England

999 9999 9999

robert.cooper@gnail.com